confirmprize.com 2002-08-02

# ConfirmPrize.com

|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
| 

Privacy Policy:

|   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
| 

Registration Information  
When you register with ConfirmPrize.com you provide name, address, zip code, email address, phone number, and birth date via an unencrypted connection to the internet. Birth date is used to ensure that all entrants are of legal age. The remaining contact information is necessary for us to deliver the products or services that you have selected, and to contact you if you have won one of our special promotions. 

|   
| 

Other Information  

To provide you with offers that are relevant to you it is necessary to, from time to time, ask you for additional information. This includes demographics, interests, hobbies, and related information. If you do not provide this information you may miss out on a special offer that you would like to receive.   
  
| 

Use of Information  
ConfirmPrize.com uses the information described above to do, among other things, the following: Deliver personalized offers, prizes, and information that are relevant to you, based on the information you have provided, from ConfirmPrize.com and our selected and trusted third party advertisers. Contact members for feedback on products and services provided by ConfirmPrize.com and our advertising partners. 

|   
| 

Opt-Out  
Members who want to opt-out from all future communications from ConfirmPrize.com and our advertising partners should send a blank e-mail to unsubscribe@confirmprize.com. The request will be completed in 5 business days. 

|   
| 

Disclosure  
In general, ConfirmPrize.com does not disclose personally identifiable information to any third party without first providing members with an opportunity to opt-out except in special situations. We may be required by law to disclose personally identifiable information to private institutions, government, or law enforcement officials to support the legal process. In the event that all or substantially all of ConfirmPrize.com stock and/or assets are transferred or sold to another entity, ConfirmPrize.com may transfer personally identifiable information to the acquiring entity. 

ConfirmPrize will prosecute any fraudulent activities to the full extent of the law. 

|   
|  |   
|  |   
|  |   
| 

**Your Entry for ConfirmPrize.com's Contest is valid only for one month, and you can return at any time to Register again after that months contest WINNER is drawn.** **GOOD LUCK & Visit Again Soon!!**

|   
| 

Privacy Policy Copyright © 2002-2004 ConfirmPrize.com, all rights reserved. Reproduction in whole or in part in any form or medium without the expressed written permission of ConfirmPrize.com is prohibited. 

|
